jodohost.com 2018-11-02

# Windows Hosting, Reseller Hosting, ASP.NET Servers - JodoHost

In order to ensure strict privacy of all our customers and site users, we have implemented a Privacy Policy. All handling of identifiable and non-identifiable customer and user information is done according to the provisions in this Policy 

**Ordering**

We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name, phone number and email address) and billing information. This information is used for billing purposes and to contact customers from time to time (see **Email Updates** section). If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the customer. IP address is logged for fraud verification purpose. We use the services of Authorize.net and Global Payments as our default method of accepting and processing payments via credit card. We provide them your credit card and billing information in order to process your payment. We also store your credit card information on our system, to bill you at the start of every billing period, if you choose to pay us by credit card and enter your credit card details while signing up. 

We also provide web-payment methods of PayPal.com, 2CheckOut.com and CCAvenue.com (India customer ONLY) to allow customers to pay us. We store no credit card information on our system, if you choose to pay by any of these three companies

**Cookies**

Our site uses cookies to store your login details and settings for our members area. No personal information is stored in these cookies. 

**Log Files**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Sharing**

We do not share any customer information with 3rd parties for commercial exploitation. However, your billing information and credit card information may be supplied to a 3rd party for payment processing. The 3rd parties are declared in Ordering Section. We cannot be held responsible for how the mentioned 3rd parties handle customer information. However, all the companies we deal with are reputable companies that are known to employ good business practices. We at JodoHost would find it unacceptable if any of the mentioned 3rd parties use the supplied information for anything but processing your payment.

**Links**

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Supplementation of Information**

In order for this website to properly fulfill its obligation to our customers, it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources. For example, if you place an order using your credit card, we may need to submit your billing information to a 3rd party for billing or verification.

**Email Update** s

We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from announcements, which may contain important information about their service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via e-mail or phone. We may also communicate to customers about products or services being offered by JodoHost, or its parent company (APYL Inc.). It is not possible to un-subscribe from these announcements as well. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes, or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing our Customer Support. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

JodoHost reserves the right to add, delete, or modify any provision of this Policy at any time without notice.
